(Raj:)You guys are being jerks.
(Howard:)Buddy, other than Jenny Craig,
(Howard:)you've never broken up
with a girl in your life.
(Raj:)You're one
to talk.
(Raj:)You've been complaining
about Stuart
(Raj:)living here for the past year.
(Raj:)I don't see you showing him
the door.
(Howard:)That's not the
same thing.
(Howard:)Emily's a person.
(Howard:)Stuart's more like
an infestation,
(Howard:)something you spray for.
(Raj:)Baloney, okay?
You two are
(Raj:)as afraid of hurting
someone's feelings as I am.
(Bernadette:)That's not true. We were just
laughing right in your face.
(Penny:)Thanks for cooking.
Mmm.
My pleasure.
(Penny:)That carrot
was delicious.
Yeah.
(Leonard:)I wish I'd fought harder
for the rest of 'em.
(Penny:)Still haven't heard
from her?
(Sheldon:)No, and I'm confused.
(Sheldon:)It's been nearly 24 hours.
(Sheldon:)Amy should have figured out
she's wrong by now.
(Penny:)Hey, I don't think she's wrong
(Penny:)about you going too slow
in the relationship.
(Sheldon:)Too slow?